hey guys so many people sent me this one
it was posted by math love and it got
thousands of likes so let's do it first
step I want to focus on this triangle
right here if we call this angle a we
know that a + 45 + 43 has to equal 180
and then after we subtract 45 and
subtract 43 from both sides that'll give
us a is equal to 92 so we can update
this to be
92° and then next let's focus on this
relationship right here this is called a
linear pair if we let this angle be n°
it we know that n + 92 is equal to 180°
and after we subtract 92 from both sides
we get n is equal to 88 so we can update
this there and then this angle right
here is also 88 you can either think of
it as a linear pair with the 92 or you
can think of it as vertical angles with
this 88 next let's focus on this
triangle right here let's let this angle
be D de then we know that D plus the 88
+ 24 needs to equal 180 and after we
subtract 88 and 24 from both sides we
get D is equal to 68 so we can update
this to be
68° and then if we extend this here we
have another linear pair and if we make
this y Dees then the y + 68 needs to
equal 180 and then we can subtract 68
from both sides and we get Y is equal to
112 and next let's focus on this
triangle right here we can call this
angle M and then once again we can do
all this math and we find that m is
equal to
66 so then we have this linear pair
right here so we know that t + 66 = 180
or in other words T is equal to 114 and
now we're down to this convex
quadrilateral right here we know that
all four of these angles are going to
add to
360° well 112 + 114 + 92 is equal to 318
and then after we subtract 318 from both
sides we get X is equal to 42 and that
is the answer to the question let's put
a box around it how exciting